<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour 042</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_about">About 042</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_churches">Churches</string>
    <string name="category_malls">Malls</string>

    //Hotels
    <string name="about_heading">About 042 (Enugu)</string>
    <string name="about_body">Enugu popularly known as 042 is the capital of Enugu State in Nigeria. It is located in
        southeastern Nigeria. The city had a population of 722,664 according to the 2006 Nigerian
        census. The name Enugu is derived from the two Igbo words Énú Ụ́gwụ́ meaning "hill top"
        denoting the hilly geography of the city. The city was named after Enugwu Ngwo, under which
        coal was found.
        In 1900 the Southern Nigeria Protectorate was established by the colonial administration
        of the British Empire. The discovery of coal by the colonialists led to the building of
        the Eastern Line railway to carry coal from the inland city to the port of Port Harcourt,
        a city created for this purpose located 151 miles (243 km) south[11] of what was called
        Enugu Coal Camp. Enugu was then renamed simply Enugu and developed as one of the few cities
        in West Africa created from European contact. By 1958 Enugu had over 8,000 coal miners.
        As of 2005 there are no significant coal mining activities left in the city.

Enugu became the capital of the Eastern Region after Nigeria's independence in 1960; a succession
        of territorial adjustments in 1967, 1976 and 1991 led to Enugu becoming the capital of what
        is now Enugu State. On 30 May 1967 Enugu was declared the capital of the short-lived
        Republic of Biafra; for this Enugu is known as the "capital of Igboland."

 The main educational establishment in the city is the Enugu campus of the University of Nigeria
        based in Nsukka, a town north of Enugu and in the same state
    Enugu city covers three local government areas: Enugu East, Enugu North and Enugu South</string>

    <string name="hotel_golden_title">Golden Royal</string>
    <string name="hotel_golden_info">Golden Royale Hotel has a sound management team with
        professionalism and a spirit of innovation when it comes to meeting and exceeding customer
        expectations. This hotel is located at 10 Bissala Road, Independence Layout, Enugu, Nigeria.
With 88 exquisitely furnished rooms and suite on 3 floors, Golden Royale provides the solution to
        all your accommodation and conference requirements.  These rooms are categorised into
        Classic, Royal Suites and the Penthouse. Each room is furnished and equipped with
        air-conditioning units, framed paintings, satellite connected flat screen TV, refrigerator,
        telephone, bedside lamp and an en-suite bathroom that feature a power shower. Complimentary
        breakfast is served daily.
Golden Royale has a couple of facilities put in place for its guests. These facilities include bars
        and restaurant offering Mediterranean and local cuisine, WI-FI internet facility, fully
        equipped gym, a sauna where guests can enjoy a steam bath with an outdoor adult and
        children swimming pool; the conference centre has ultra-modern state-of-the-art facilities.
        This hotel boasts 24hrs police patrol and in-house security presence as well as CCTV cameras.
Additional services rendered by the hotel include 24hrs room service, airport shuttle, car hire,
        laundry/dry cleaning and business services.For more information and reservation visit
        https://www.goldenroyalehotels.com
    </string>
    
    <string name="hotel_cordial_title">Cordial Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_cordial_info">Constructed in a stylish fashion and equipped with modern
        facilities, Hotel Codial is a boutique hotel located at 151 Chime Avenue, New Haven,
        Enugu, Nigeria. It is in the low-density area of New Haven, Enugu State.
The fenced hotel premises has well-furnished rooms that are of varying categories. These categories
        are Super Single, Super Double, Executive Single and Executive Double Rooms. Each room is
        designated as non-smoking areas and feature full air-conditioning, a king-sized bed, cable
        enabled flat screen TV, safety deposit box and an en-suite bathroom.
Hotel Codial boasts facilities such as free Wi-Fi, swimming pool, a fitness centre/gym, 24 hours
        facilities, free adequate parking space, 24 hours front desk service, a restaurant that
        serves from a wide list of local, Chinese and other continental cuisines, and a
        cocktail/public/open sky bar where guests can get access to assorted snacks and a variety
        of both alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks. Hotel Codial has security personnel that ensure
        the safety of guests and their properties.
Additional services offered on request by Hotel Codial include contract catering services, a
        conference hall with a 500 person capacity, a gift shop, laundry/dry cleaning, car hire,
        ironing and 24 hours room service. For more information on reservation and booking visit
        https://hotels.ng/hotel/92787-hotel-codial-enugu</string>
    
    <string name="hotel_gate_title">The Gate Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_gate_info">At The Gates Luxury Apartment we are proud to serve and create
        an ambiance that will make you feel calm and relaxed. We provide the best personalized
        service from professional staff to exceed the need of our esteemed guests. Together with
        tastefully furnished Apartments we pride ourselves in providing you with excellent service
        at competitive price.
The Gates is an American franchise under Zivama Hospitality Ltd. The Gates Apartment is located in
        the popular Zoo Estate by Ogui Junction, in Enugu North LGA of Enugu State; about 10 minute
        drive from Enugu International Airport. The Gates is within a serene environment; is the
        ideal place for lodging, banquets, and executive meetings. The elegant garden bar of the
        gates can provide natural scenery, beauty and relaxation. The Gates has a conference room
        that is fully equipped and furnished to taste.
Breakfast, lunch or dinner is available on request where delicious buffets are served, enjoy exotic
        cocktails at our bars and feel totally relaxed.
The Apartment hosts outstanding facilities together with a friendly and professional staff to serve
        you better.
- See more at: http://thegates.com.ng/about-us/#sthash.Bp7npOrS.dpuf </string>
    
    <string name="hotel_adig_title">Adig Suites</string>
    <string name="hotel_adig_info">Adig Suites is a top class 4-star hotel situated at 2 Nwafor
        Orizu Street, Independence Layout, Enugu, Nigeria. It’s a tourist favourite due to its
        proximity to the Ngwo Pine Forest.
Adig Suites has rooms with classy and home feel with designs incorporating modern furnishing.
        Room categories include Superior Room, Executive Room, Junior Suite and Executive Suite.
        Some rooms have a view overlooking the city. Each room features a spacious bathroom,
        king-sized beds, cable connected LCD TV sets, refrigerators and air conditioners.
At the Adig Suites, rooms contain a desk. All rooms are equipped with an electric tea pot, while
        some rooms also feature a kitchenette with a fridge. All rooms feature a closet.
A number of facilities are available Adig Suites Hotel. These include free WiFi, a swimming pool,
        a body spa, a restaurant and a bar. Guests at this hotel will have more time to enjoy their
        stay at the hotel.
The hotel offers additional services on request such as 24-hour front desk, shuttle service,
        Concierge service, Luggage storage, Express check-in/check-out, Cleaning services,
        Room service, Event Hall, Free Parking Space, Ironing service, Designated Smoking Area,
        Hypoallergenic Room Available, Convenience Store, Car Rental, Souvenir/Gift Shop, Safe,
        Elevator, Honeymoon Suite, VIP Room Facilities, Family Rooms, Dry cleaning/Laundry service
        and business centre.</string>
    
    <string name="hotel_oaklands_title">Oaklands Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_oaklands_info">Oakland Hotels and Amusement Park is a top-class hotel
        located at Tunnel Crossing, Ogui Link Road, Beside Elim Plaza, Enugu, Nigeria. The hotel
        offers affordable accommodation to guests.
Guests will enjoy a complimentary breakfast.
Each room at Oakland Hotels and Amusement Park has a study desk, an air conditioner, free WiFi, and
        king-sized beds.
Also available at the hotel are a restaurant and a bar.
Guests can enjoy different meals at the restaurant on site.
Services available include Room service, Cleaning services.
In addition, guests can also enjoy Luggage storage on request.
    For more information or reservation visit
        https://hotels.ng/hotel/1391127-oakland-hotels-and-amusement-park</string>
    
    //Restaurants
    <string name="res_dolphin_title">Dolphin Restaurant</string>
    <string name="res_dolphin_info">Dolphin Restaurant is an African Restaurant and bar in the 
        heart of the Coal City. They have been serving customers since more than 30 years. 
        Initially, they started the restaurant services under the name of Madam Volvo. The 
        Restaurant is a perfect place for lunch, dinner or for having any kind of party. Dolphin
        principles are to combine the highest quality and authentic African food with excellent 
        customer service at great value for money, all served in a comfortable ambience.
        For more information visit http://www.dolphinrestaurantng.com</string>
    
    <string name="res_ntachi_title">Ntachi Osa</string>
    <string name="res_ntachi_info">Passing by the Coal city or looking for a place to enjoy good
        homely delicacies, relax and blow off some steam?. Then walk into this first grade
        restaurant that offers the best varieties of quality African and continental meals, drinks
        and first class services.
        Ntachi Osa sells delicious African and continental dishes. We are one of Enugu state
        standard restaurant with good food management, well prepared and neatly served food for
        your delight.</string>

    <string name="res_kililmanjaro_title">Kilimanjaro</string>
    <string name="res_kililmanjaro_info">Kilimanjaro is one of Sundry Foods’ restaurant brands,
        operating in the Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) segment, the brand has established itself
        as a market leader and one of the fastest growing restaurant brands in the country with
        currently 27 stores across Nigeria and more to come.
        Kilimanjaro caters to the unique preference of the general populace in this part of sub-Saharan
        Africa for their local dishes. Our unique menu consists of select popular contemporary and
        Nigerian offerings. Items on our menu can also be found on dining tables in other African
        countries. The Kilimanjaro brand was born out the quest to satisfy both local and
        continental food cravings of our people. We deliver fresh, hot and mouth-watering meals,
        pastries, sandwiches and beverages to thousands of customers in the finest environment each
        day. Our restaurants stand out for their bright colours and lovely ambience inviting you to
        dine-in or grab-and-go with the best quality meals. In Enugu we located at
        -Polopark Mall
        POLOPARK MALL, ABAKAILIKI ROAD, OLD GRA, ENUGU.
        070054543663.
        callcenter@sundryfood.com
        -Enugu Mall
        Enugu Mall, Independence Layout. Enugu
        callcenter@sundryfood.com
</string>

    <string name="res_crunches_title">Crunchies</string>
    <string name="res_crunches_info">CRUNCHIES FRIED CHICKEN is a first grade quick service
        restaurant that offers the best varieties of quality fast food products and first class
        services. We are currently spread across the South-South and South-East Cities of Nigeria,
        with over thirteen years’ experience. We have carved a niche of excellence in the fast food
        delivery market with a service per excellence acquired from our daily interaction from our
        valued Customers.
        Crunchies Fried Chicken, Enugu is located at 4/5 Rangers Avenue, Enugu, Enugu.</string>

    <string name="res_roots_title">Roots Restaurant</string>
    <string name="res_roots_info">Roots Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most celebrated African
        cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and heritage in an
        environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant and Cafe is
        powered by Crunchies Fried Chicken. Over many years of customer service experience and
        careful study of healthy eating habits, we have opened new doors to a larger variety of
        menus to provide a list of African diets with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    //Churches
    <string name="church_catholic_title">The Roman Catholic Church</string>
    <string name="church_catholic_info">The Roman Catholic Diocese of Enugu is a diocese located in
        the city of Enugu in the Ecclesiastical province of Onitsha in Nigeria. On November 12,
        1962, the Diocese of Enugu was erected from ecclesiastical territory gained from the
        Metropolitan Archdiocese of Onitsha. The Cathedral is Holy Ghost Cathedral in Enugu. There
        are about 53 Catholic parishes in Enugu, we have
        -New Haven (St. Mulumba)
        -Ekulu, G.R.A. (Christ the King)
        -Golf Estate (Holy Spirit)
        -Ind. Layout (Blessed Sacrament)
        -Uwani (Sacred Heart)
        Visit http://catholicdioceseenugu.org for more information.
    </string>

    <string name="church_anglican_title">The Anglican Communion</string>
    <string name="church_anglican_info">Welcome to the diocese of Enugu. Anglican communion is a
        reputable church in the heart of Enugu well positioned at major places around the city.
        The Anglican Province of Enugu is one of the 14 ecclesiastical provinces of the Church of
        Nigeria. The province comprises 12 dioceses. The Archbishop of the Province of Enugu is
        Emmanuel Chukwuma, who succeeded Amos Madu in 2014. The has it's state province located at
        Archbishop's Court, No 40 Nawfia Street, Independence Layout, Enugu, Nigeria.</string>

    <string name="church_assemblies_title">Assembles of God</string>
    <string name="church_assemblies_info">Assemblies of God is widely known as the mother of
    pentecostalism in Nigeria. The church in Enugu is headed by the Rev. Dr. Emmanuel Ngene as the
    district superintendent of Enugu. The church has more than 20 branches across the city but the
    head church is located at No. 66 Chime Avenue New Haven, Enugu. The church has other branches
    at Abakpa, Trans-ekulu, emene, G.R.A, Independence Layout, Uwani and so on.</string>

    <string name="church_winners_title">Winners Chapel</string>
    <string name="church_winners_info">Winners Roots Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    <string name="church_hodr_title">House On The Rock</string>
    <string name="church_hodr_info">House On The Rock Roots Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    //Malls
    <string name="mall_polo_title">Polo Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_polo_info">Polo Roots Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    <string name="mall_enugu_title">Enugu Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_enugu_info">Enugu Mall Roots Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    <string name="mall_roban_title">Roban Stores</string>
    <string name="mall_roban_info">Roban stores Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    <string name="mall_eastern_title">Eastern Shop</string>
    <string name="mall_eastern_info">Eastern Shop Restaurant and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

    <string name="mall_best_title">Best Choice Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_best_info">Best Choice Shopping Mall and Cafe is one of the most
        celebrated African cuisine restaurants in Nigeria, bringing in rich African culture and
        heritage in an environment that is welcoming, clean and comforting.The Roots restaurant
        and Cafe ispowered by Crunchies Fried Chicken.
        Over many years of customer service experience and careful study of healthy eating habits,
        we have opened new doors to a larger variety of menus to provide a list of African diets
        with a mix of other foreign influences such as
        All-day breakfast, Chinese Cuisines, Continental Dishes and Cafe. Using the best natural
        cooking ingredients, our kitchen produces the most nourishing local and continental dishes
        for healthy living. In Enugu we are located at Plot M 23c Independence Layout, Opposite
        Okpara Square, Beside SPAR. For more information call +234 9063930915 or visit
        https://www.roots.com.ng</string>

</resources>
